http://www.mstworld.com/privacy_policy

ServicesSectorsAboutContactCloseServicesBackAll ServicesBroadcast GraphicsGraphics Build and IntegrationOff / On-site SupportBranding / Web and AppBroadcast Graphic DesignRemote Production GraphicsSports Data SystemsData ManagementData IntegrationBroadcast ServicesOperatorsApplicationsHardwareMultiple FeedsAnalysis SystemsCG HireChyron HireVizrt HireGraphics HireSectorsBackGolfBasketballOtherServicesSectorsAboutTestimonialsFAQCareersContactServicesSectorsAboutContactTESTIMONIALSCAREERSFAQServicesBackAll ServicesBroadcast GraphicsGraphics Build and IntegrationOff / On-site SupportBranding / Web and AppBroadcast Graphic DesignRemote Production GraphicsSports Data SystemsData ManagementData IntegrationBroadcast ServicesOperatorsApplicationsHardwareMultiple FeedsAnalysis SystemsCG HireChyron HireVizrt HireGraphics HireSectorsBackAll SectorsBasketballGolfOtherTESTIMONIALSCAREERSFAQPrivacy PolicyHome / Privacy PolicyPrivacy policy at MST SYSTEMS Ltd (MST)We respect the privacy of visitors to our website (www.mstworld.com). This policy is concerned with how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have over your personal information.Your privacyMST offers the complete sports timing, scoring and analysis solution for any size or type of event. Using the latest technology, innovative ideas and expert personnel, MST provides a professional and reliable package with novel solutions to unique challenges.We take our duty to process your personal information very seriously. This policy explains how we collect, manage, use an protect your personal information.We may change this document from time to time to reflect the latest view of what we do with your information. Please check back frequently; you will be able to see if changes have been made by the date it was last updated.Refer to the sections below for more details on how and why we use your personal information:1. Who are we?MST is a Private limited Company registered in England and Wales. Registered Company Number: 03020101.2. What personal information we collect and how we use itWhat we needMST is what's known as the 'controller' of the personal information you provide to us. We will usually collect basic personal information about you like your name, postal address, telephone number and email address.We will be very clear with you that we wish to collect such information, our reason for collecting such information, and we would only do so with your consent.Why we need itWe collect your personal information in connection with responding to your website contact. We may also collect information as part of providing a service to you (for example, hiring a transponder to you at a motorsport event).The information is either needed to fulfil your request or to enable us to provide you with a more personalised service. You don't have to disclose any of this information to browse our site. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.Our marketingSometimes, with your consent, we will process your personal information to provide you with information about our work or our activities that you have requested or are expecting.On other occasions, we may process personal information when we need to do this to fulfil a contract (for example, if you are attending an event) or where we are required to do this by law or other regulations.MST also processes your information when it is in our legitimate interests to do this and when these interests do not override your rights. Please see the section on 'Legitimate Interest' for more information.How we obtain your detailsWe will also hold information about you so that we can respect your preferences for being contacted by us.We collect your personal information in a number of ways:When you provide it to us directly.When you provide permission to other organisations to share it with us.When you provide permission to other organisations to share it with us e.g. Twitter, Facebook.When we collect it as you use our website – see Section 6 for details of our cookie policy.Anything else?The personal information we process may be processed outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). This includes for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance. This will be done in accordance with guidance issued by the Information Commissioner's Office.3. Legitimate interestsWe have a number of lawful reasons that mean we can use your personal information. One of these is something called 'legitimate interests'. Broadly speaking Legitimate Interests means we can process your personal information if:We have a genuine and legitimate reason, and we are not harming any of your rights and interests.4. Sharing your informationWe do not share your information with any other organisations or individuals unless we are obliged to by law, for purposes of national security, taxation and criminal investigations and in the following instances:* If you have agreed that we may do so.* When we use other companies to provide services on our behalf, e.g. processing, mailing or delivering orders, sending mail and emails, customer analysis, assessment, when using auditors/advisors or processing credit/debit card payments.* To our related companies.* If we merge with another organisation to form a new entity, information may be transferred to the new entity.* We may disclose aggregate statistics about our site visitors, supporters, customers and sales to describe our services and operations to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics won’t include any personally identifying information.* If we run an event in partnership with other named organisations your details may need to be shared. We will be very clear what will happen to your data when you register.And, we will never sell or rent your personal information to other organisations.5. Retaining your informationWe hold your information only as long as necessary for each reason that we use it. We have provided some examples of the time we will keep your information in this paragraph but you can contact us for more information.If you request that we have no further contact with you, we will keep some basic information in order to avoid sending you unwanted information in the future and to ensure that we don’t accidentally duplicate information.If you make a hire from us, we will keep the purchase information for a period of seven years for accounting purposes.6. Our cookie policyThis policy explains what cookies are, how MST uses them on our websites and what you can do to manage how they are used.Cookies and how they benefit youOur website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites.Our cookies help us:* Make our website work as you'd expect.* Remember your settings during and between visits.* Improve the speed/security of the site.* Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook.* Continuously improve our website for you.Granting us permission to use cookies.If the settings on your browser that you are using to view this website are adjusted to accept cookies we take this, and your continued use of our website, to mean that you are fine with this. Should you wish to remove or not use cookies from our site you can learn how to do this below, however doing so will likely mean that our site will not work as you would expect.How long do cookies last?* Some date in the future – which might be a few minutes or a few hours from now (to track something like your shopping cart in an online store). The cookie might expire many years in the future, to keep track of your browser for a long time.* When you close your browser – this is called a session cookie, the next time you start your browser these will have vanished.* Some date in the past – this is how the server asks a browser to remove a previously-stored cookie.Anonymous visitor statistics cookiesWe use cookies to compile visitor statistics such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using, how long they spend on the site, what page they look at, etc. This helps us to continuously improve our website. These analytics programs also tell us, on an anonymous basis, how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before, helping us to to develop our services for you.Our site uses the following analytics programs:Google analyticsAdvertising or targeting cookiesThese types of cookies are used to deliver adverts which will be more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement and to help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are normally placed by advertising networks with the organisation's permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Targeting or advertising cookies will often be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.Turning cookies offYou can usually switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies. Doing so, however, will likely limit the functionality of ours and a large proportion of the world's websites as cookies are a standard part of most modern websites.7. What are your rights?You have a number of rights about how the personal information you provide can be used. These are:* Transparency over how we use your personal information (right to be informed).* The ability to request a copy of the information we hold about you, which will be provided to you within one month (right of access).* Update or amend the information we hold about you if it is wrong (right of rectification).* Ask us to stop using your information (right to restrict processing).* Ask us to remove your personal information from our records (right to be 'forgotten').* Object to the processing of your information for marketing purposes (right to object).* Obtain and reuse your personal information for your own purposes (right to data portability).* Not be subject to a decision when it is based on automated processing (automated decision making and profiling).If you would like to know more about your rights under the data protection law, you can find out more at the Information Commissioner’s Office website.Remember, you can change the way you hear from us or withdraw your permission for us to processing your personal information at any time by using the form on our 'Contact Us' page.8. How to contact usIf you wish to talk through anything in our privacy policy, find out more about your rights or obtain a copy of the information we hold about you, please contact us (details at the bottom of this page), we will be happy to help.If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal information, you can contact our Office Manager who will investigate the matter. If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal information in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).If you wish to talk to us about anything in the policy or the information we hold about you please contact us:By telephone: +44 (0) 1684 560614By email: admin@mstworld.comBy post: MST SYSTEMS Ltd, Indigo House, The Haysfield, Spring Lane North, Malvern Link, England, WR14 1GFThis document was last updated: August 201801 Services02 Sectors03 AboutTestimonialsCareersFAQContact usMST SYSTEMS LtdIndigo HouseThe HaysfieldMalvernWorcestershire. UKWR14 1GFt: +44 (0) 1684 560 614e: admin@mstworld.comPrivacy PolicyMST SYSTEMS Ltd. © Copyright 2020
